Select Page

Privacy policy
==============

1\. General
-----------

This privacy policy (hereinafter referred to as – the “Privacy Policy”) is for this website VPNTunnel.com (hereinafter referred to as – the “Website”) and served by VPNTunnel.com and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.

This Privacy Policy sets out the different areas where user’s privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations and requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user’s data and information will also be detailed within this policy.  
By using VPNTunnel.com services or website, you agree that you consent to this Privacy Policy and any changes hereto in the future.

2\. The website
---------------

This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all Seychelles national laws and requirements for user privacy.

3\. Security
------------

Proceeding from the specificity of our services we value our users data confidentiality most of all.  
To maximize user’s privacy, we collect the minimum information required specifically:

* E-mail Address we receive from user (to identify user in our network, to send subscription information, payment confirmations, customer correspondence, and promotional offers)
* Payment data (to analyze chosen method of payment in order to improve transactions process in better way and to solve any problems that may occur with third party payment processor, to manage client signups, payments, and cancellations; VPNTunnel.com doesn’t collect any bank data, because all physical payment in order to access VPNTunnel.com are made by intermediary societies (e.g. PayPal, Plimus).
* Google analytics data (appears anonymous) (to improve our website).  
    – Submissions on the ‘Contact Us’ page (for correspondence).  
    – User’s cookies (only for advertising purposes in order to analyze advertising trends and administer the site properly).  
    We do not need user’s name or surname, physical addresses, phone number or any other personal identifying information, and we will never ask our users for any personal data.
* We NEVER keep online activity logs or store private information about individual user activities on our network. Information regarding payments may be logged, as per payment processor regulations.

4\. Disclosure of user’s information
------------------------------------

VPNTunnel.com may disclose users personal information to third parties if

* VPNTunnel.com is, or all of its assets are, acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its users will be one of the transferred assets, but will remain covered by this Privacy Policy.
* VPNTunnel.com is under a duty to disclose user’s data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce VPNTunnel.com Terms of Service; or to protect the rights, property, or VPNTunnel.com safety and VPNTunnel.com.

5\. Changes to the privacy policy
---------------------------------

You agree that VPNTunnel.com has the right to change this privacy policy at any time without any given notice at its discretion by posting such changes on the website. But VPNTunnel.com will take every reasonable step to notify users by email.

6\. Disputes
------------

These Privacy Policy and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it or its subject matter shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of Seychelles.

7\. Feedback and questions
--------------------------

Any comments or suggestions that you may have and which may contribute to a better quality of service will be welcome and greatly appreciated.

#### About

More and more people are choosing VPNTunnel as their VPN service provider.

We are incredibly proud of this and our ambition is to expand globally whilst continuing to offer a stable and secure VPN service.

#### VPNTunnel

#### Supported OS

* Mac OS X
* Linux
* Ubuntu
* Steam
* Playstation

#### Follow Us

Digital Sales Solutions LLC © 2021 All Rights Reserved  
3401 SIRIUS AVE NUM 3227, LAS VEGAS, NV 89102
